[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "What was the first that you heard that made you realize there was a big event happening right outside?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "first", "that", "you", "heard", "that", "made", "you", "realize", "there", "was", "a", "big", "event", "happening", "right", "outside", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "A huge siren.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "huge", "siren", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy Yard"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What are you hearing about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "hearing", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "they're absolutely could be, I mean there are always, there's always second guessing in situations like this, but I believe given the route that she took from to very important places of power with very -- with a lot of security and law enforcement protecting people and particularly after what happened in 9/11 and the scare even most recently at the Navy Yard, I think everybody was, I know everybody was on high alert.", "answer_tokens": ["they", "'re", "absolutely", "could", "be", ",", "I", "mean", "there", "are", "always", ",", "there", "'s", "always", "second", "guessing", "in", "situations", "like", "this", ",", "but", "I", "believe", "given", "the", "route", "that", "she", "took", "from", "to", "very", "important", "places", "of", "power", "with", "very", "--", "with", "a", "lot", "of", "security", "and", "law", "enforcement", "protecting", "people", "and", "particularly", "after", "what", "happened", "in", "9/11", "and", "the", "scare", "even", "most", "recently", "at", "the", "Navy", "Yard", ",", "I", "think", "everybody", "was", ",", "I", "know", "everybody", "was", "on", "high", "alert", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WDT", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "When did you realize what had happened and what was your first fear?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "realize", "what", "had", "happened", "and", "what", "was", "your", "first", "fear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well Piers, when we're walking outside which usually when I leave that Thursday lunch, we -- I usually walk underground, this just happened to be outside but the first thought that I had, the initial thought when I heard all the sirens and the law enforcement, I thought it was a dignitary being escorted then as I got closer to that corner, I knew there was more urgency to it and then I heard about three or four pops of gunfire, of course then, we knew it was very serious.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "Piers", ",", "when", "we", "'re", "walking", "outside", "which", "usually", "when", "I", "leave", "that", "Thursday", "lunch", ",", "we", "--", "I", "usually", "walk", "underground", ",", "this", "just", "happened", "to", "be", "outside", "but", "the", "first", "thought", "that", "I", "had", ",", "the", "initial", "thought", "when", "I", "heard", "all", "the", "sirens", "and", "the", "law", "enforcement", ",", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "dignitary", "being", "escorted", "then", "as", "I", "got", "closer", "to", "that", "corner", ",", "I", "knew", "there", "was", "more", "urgency", "to", "it", "and", "then", "I", "heard", "about", "three", "or", "four", "pops", "of", "gunfire", ",", "of", "course", "then", ",", "we", "knew", "it", "was", "very", "serious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "What else did I call them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "did", "I", "call", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "The weird caucus.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "weird", "caucus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "So I mean do you think -- are you pledging to tone down the rhetoric a little bit and maybe that could help?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "mean", "do", "you", "think", "--", "are", "you", "pledging", "to", "tone", "down", "the", "rhetoric", "a", "little", "bit", "and", "maybe", "that", "could", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I'm not going to give up on the anarchist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "give", "up", "on", "the", "anarchist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Are the Republicans now if they -- well if we can keep it going 'till then we can do some kind of grand recovery plan which can get us off the wrap here?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "the", "Republicans", "now", "if", "they", "--", "well", "if", "we", "can", "keep", "it", "going", "'till", "then", "we", "can", "do", "some", "kind", "of", "grand", "recovery", "plan", "which", "can", "get", "us", "off", "the", "wrap", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "You know, the Speaker and his leaders aren't talking about ObamaCare and getting rid of ObamaCare as far as negotiating is going in public.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "Speaker", "and", "his", "leaders", "are", "n't", "talking", "about", "ObamaCare", "and", "getting", "rid", "of", "ObamaCare", "as", "far", "as", "negotiating", "is", "going", "in", "public", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "How do you feel as a Democratic Senator, do you feel powerless at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "as", "a", "Democratic", "Senator", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "powerless", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think right now, there are two basic facts I think that are operative here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "think", "right", "now", ",", "there", "are", "two", "basic", "facts", "I", "think", "that", "are", "operative", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Is it Speaker Boehner or Ted Cruz?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "Speaker", "Boehner", "or", "Ted", "Cruz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, I couldn't tell you where it is in the Senate side of things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "tell", "you", "where", "it", "is", "in", "the", "Senate", "side", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner", "Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What is your biggest fear going forward?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "biggest", "fear", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, my greatest fear is getting further and further into debt and not being able to climb out and also not being able to pay the bills, put food on the table, pay for the medications my daughter needs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "greatest", "fear", "is", "getting", "further", "and", "further", "into", "debt", "and", "not", "being", "able", "to", "climb", "out", "and", "also", "not", "being", "able", "to", "pay", "the", "bills", ",", "put", "food", "on", "the", "table", ",", "pay", "for", "the", "medications", "my", "daughter", "needs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Does that help you that knowledge or if this goes on for few weeks, does the pain you suffer in that short- term period just be really very difficult to handle?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "help", "you", "that", "knowledge", "or", "if", "this", "goes", "on", "for", "few", "weeks", ",", "does", "the", "pain", "you", "suffer", "in", "that", "short-", "term", "period", "just", "be", "really", "very", "difficult", "to", "handle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "It's going to be difficult to handle.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "difficult", "to", "handle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What do you think Mr. Penders of the way the politicians are behaving over this in Washington?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "Mr.", "Penders", "of", "the", "way", "the", "politicians", "are", "behaving", "over", "this", "in", "Washington", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I think they're behaving like a bunch of spoiled children, like a bunch of five-year-olds throwing temper tantrums especially the Republicans.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "behaving", "like", "a", "bunch", "of", "spoiled", "children", ",", "like", "a", "bunch", "of", "five-year-olds", "throwing", "temper", "tantrums", "especially", "the", "Republicans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Penders"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "You're not happy what you're hearing, why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "happy", "what", "you", "'re", "hearing", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "And what is the combined impact?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "combined", "impact", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "So President Obama didn't carry most congressional districts.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "President", "Obama", "did", "n't", "carry", "most", "congressional", "districts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Republican House"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "But what is your impression of the impact that's having right now?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "your", "impression", "of", "the", "impact", "that", "'s", "having", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Yeah, well I mean that's fine as an explanation for why we have a Republican House and a Democratic President but it's an excuse for why republicans have decided that they're going to hold hostage the normal operation of government in order to have negotiations.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "well", "I", "mean", "that", "'s", "fine", "as", "an", "explanation", "for", "why", "we", "have", "a", "Republican", "House", "and", "a", "Democratic", "President", "but", "it", "'s", "an", "excuse", "for", "why", "republicans", "have", "decided", "that", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "hold", "hostage", "the", "normal", "operation", "of", "government", "in", "order", "to", "have", "negotiations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What is your concern about what is going on right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "concern", "about", "what", "is", "going", "on", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, I have to say this is a scary situation for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "say", "this", "is", "a", "scary", "situation", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "You are a senior oncologist, you are at the sharp end of all this, what is your view?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "a", "senior", "oncologist", ",", "you", "are", "at", "the", "sharp", "end", "of", "all", "this", ",", "what", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I think especially for young Americans this is an amazing opportunity to make sure that we can treat you right, I mean the liaison (ph) therapy that happened because people don't have insurance it leads to morbidity and mortality and it's not right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "especially", "for", "young", "Americans", "this", "is", "an", "amazing", "opportunity", "to", "make", "sure", "that", "we", "can", "treat", "you", "right", ",", "I", "mean", "the", "liaison", "(", "ph", ")", "therapy", "that", "happened", "because", "people", "do", "n't", "have", "insurance", "it", "leads", "to", "morbidity", "and", "mortality", "and", "it", "'s", "not", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Head Start Program"], "LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Tell me what you are going through right now, what your particular concern is?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "what", "you", "are", "going", "through", "right", "now", ",", "what", "your", "particular", "concern", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "As of tomorrow actually the Head Start Program in Florida will be shutdown.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "of", "tomorrow", "actually", "the", "Head", "Start", "Program", "in", "Florida", "will", "be", "shutdown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "So, Star, you see, when you hear this it just makes me so bloody angry, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Star", ",", "you", "see", ",", "when", "you", "hear", "this", "it", "just", "makes", "me", "so", "bloody", "angry", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Because you're like how can you allow this to happen in America?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "'re", "like", "how", "can", "you", "allow", "this", "to", "happen", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "ONES: In America.", "answer_tokens": ["ONES", ":", "In", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Michael you're shaking your head?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", "you", "'re", "shaking", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, I think, I think -- I don't ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What is the practical reality and how we get out of this particular situation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "practical", "reality", "and", "how", "we", "get", "out", "of", "this", "particular", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Well, I think objectively we use of the terms bickering and squabbling and I think both sides are taking principal position ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "objectively", "we", "use", "of", "the", "terms", "bickering", "and", "squabbling", "and", "I", "think", "both", "sides", "are", "taking", "principal", "position", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 401, "question": "When you hear Harry Reid call them anarchists?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "Harry", "Reid", "call", "them", "anarchists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "ARONE: Yes, that was not ...", "answer_tokens": ["ARONE", ":", "Yes", ",", "that", "was", "not", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Reid"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 407, "question": "You think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "...t he House...", "answer_tokens": ["...", "t", "he", "House", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 411, "question": "You shutdown a government because you want to change parts of an established law?", "question_tokens": ["You", "shutdown", "a", "government", "because", "you", "want", "to", "change", "parts", "of", "an", "established", "law", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, I think the Republicans made a miscalculation by raising the issue of defunding ObamaCare, it polled poorly voters truly didn't want it, delay ObamaCare polls better I think that probably would have been a foolish thing for them to go on a ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "Republicans", "made", "a", "miscalculation", "by", "raising", "the", "issue", "of", "defunding", "ObamaCare", ",", "it", "polled", "poorly", "voters", "truly", "did", "n't", "want", "it", ",", "delay", "ObamaCare", "polls", "better", "I", "think", "that", "probably", "would", "have", "been", "a", "foolish", "thing", "for", "them", "to", "go", "on", "a", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Do you think what's going on to good principle politics?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "to", "good", "principle", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I think it's miscalculation by people who are principal politicians and I think ...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "miscalculation", "by", "people", "who", "are", "principal", "politicians", "and", "I", "think", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "If President Rouhani pick the telephone up and called you, would you take that call?", "question_tokens": ["If", "President", "Rouhani", "pick", "the", "telephone", "up", "and", "called", "you", ",", "would", "you", "take", "that", "call", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Yeah, we're not the first to call and it's the question I'll tell you what I'll tell him.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "we", "'re", "not", "the", "first", "to", "call", "and", "it", "'s", "the", "question", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "what", "I", "'ll", "tell", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rouhani"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "And would you hesitate to take military action?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "you", "hesitate", "to", "take", "military", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "ETANYAHU: No, I wouldn't.", "answer_tokens": ["ETANYAHU", ":", "No", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "... damage the global economy?", "question_tokens": ["...", "damage", "the", "global", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes, they'll work it out.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "'ll", "work", "it", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]